KARL **GENTNER**

QUALITY ENGINEER RPA DEVELOPER

gentnerkarl@gmail.com



kgentner.github.io



(206) 499-5011



Seattle, WA

In linkedin.com/in/karlgentner

SKILLS

UIPATH RPA

STUDIO ORCHESTRATOR **TEST MANAGER INSIGHTS** PROCESS LAUNCHER **AUTOMATION HUB** TASK CAPTURE

FRONT-END

SELENIUM CODED UI **JAVASCRIPT** HTML5 **BOOTSTRAP**

BACK-END

VB.NET C.# .NET MVC HTTP REST API SOL

OTHER

AZURE DEVOPS **POSTMAN** CI/CD PIPELINE VISUAL STUDIO CODE **POWER AUTOMATE**

SUMMARY

Engineer with 9 years of experience in RPA (robotic process automation), test automation, and software development for internal enterprise business groups. Currently focused on the UiPath Platform, I am a versatile and enthusiastic team member with strong communication skills, a passion for learning new technologies, and the analytical capability for complex problem-solving and technical investigation.

PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS

EPIC HYPERSPACE TEST AUTOMATION

RPA + TEST AUTOMATION

- · Lead developer and scrum master for an on-going program that creates RPA and test automation for Providence's electronic medical records system (EMR), Epic Hyperspace.
- Trained and mentored 5-person team in UiPath RPA development, implementing best practices, establishing SDLC guidelines and sprint cadence, and performing regular code reviews.
- · Provided technical guidance and solution support to both business and engineering stakeholders as a Providence UiPath administrator and subject-matter expert (SME).
- Developed custom framework and libraries to enable rapid expansion of new processes and enhancements, resulting in an average savings of over 100 manual resource hours per month.
- Developed UiPath-based monitoring solution for system-wide Citrix deployments, reducing engineering resources for go-live events by 85%.

Technologies: UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, UiPath Citrix Runtime

PROJECT ONLINE PMO AUTOMATION

RPA + TEST AUTOMATION

- Developed an automated solution for migrating intake projects from Dynamics CRM to Project Online, resulting in the automated creation of over 500 projects a year.
- Developed automated resource group and timecard creation for downstream integration testing with Oracle Genesis ERP, reducing manual work by 80% per iteration and increasing quality of high-impact labor capitalization process.

Technologies: UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, Project Online OData API, JSON

MIRA INSURANCE REFERENCE APPLICATION

CUSTOM WEB APPLICATION

- Worked directly with Providence Revenue Cycle to design and develop a web application to help the staff of clinics and hospitals accurately register patient insurance.
- Managed time efficiently to ensure punctual delivery for testing and production roll-out dates.

Technologies: .NET MVC, Entity Framework, Bootstrap, and SQL

EMPLOYMENT

- Quality Engineer Renton, WA
- Software Developer Seattle, WA
- **QA Analyst Renton, WA**
- **Acoustical Consultant -** Seattle, WA BRC Acoustics / Pressure Wave
- Recording Engineer Atlanta, GA
- Providence St. Joseph Health
- Self-employed
- Providence Health & Services
- 11.2006 10.2014

• 03.2019 - Present

04.2017 - 02.2019

05.2015 - 03.2017

• R!OT Atlanta / Sync Sound • 04.1998 - 08.2005

EDUCATION

Code Fellows - Seattle, WA

Rensselaer Polytechnic - Troy, NY

Florida State University - Tallahassee, FL • BA: American Studies

- CERT: Full-Stack JavaScript
- MS: Architectural Acoustics
- 10.2014 12.2014
- 08.2005 12.2006
- 08.1991 12.1995